[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- So, what do you kids think
- 那么，你们这些孩子们觉得
of the new Thirsty War smoothie menu?
新出的Thirsty War果汁菜单怎么样？
- I think it's a shameless attempt
- 我觉得这是无耻地试图
to make money off the new "Hungry Wars" movie
从这周末上映的新电影《Hungry Wars》中赚钱。
that's coming out this weekend.
- 你说得没错。
- And you would be correct.
这就是为什么你将来会接管家族生意的原因。
That's why you're taking over the family business someday.
- 你知道，我确实有一些想法--
- You know, I do have some ideas-- - I said someday.
- 我说的是将来某一天。
- Oh, I see you named a smoothie after Ganderk the Great.
- 哦，我看到你用Ganderk the Great的名字命名了一款果汁。
- Who's Ganderk the Great?
- 谁是Ganderk the Great？
- Only the most powerful Gnome Fairy in all of Gardenia.
- 他可是Gardenia里最强大的侏儒仙子。
- And maybe the entire Middle Universe?
- 或许在整个中间宇宙也是？
- And their favorite "Hungry Wars" character.
- 还是他们最喜欢的“饥饿战争”角色。
- Oh, two Ganderk the Grape smoothies, please.
- 哦，请来两杯Ganderk the Grape奶昔。
- That Ganderk dude has cool hair.
- 那个Ganderk的家伙发型很酷。
Just like Dicky the Grape.
就像Dicky the Grape一样。
- You just called yourself a grape.
- 你刚刚称自己为葡萄了。
- I know.
- 我知道。
- Ooh, Mr. Harper.
- 哦，Harper先生。
Not to nitpick, but you spelled Ganderk wrong.
不是吹毛求疵，但你把Ganderk拼错了。
And also, in the last movie,
而且，在上部电影里，
Ganderk is poisoned by grapes,
Ganderk是被葡萄毒死的，
so this is a double fail.
所以这是双重失败。
- You're a double fail!
- 你是双重失败！
Sorry, I'm just-- I worked really hard on this menu...
对不起，我只是——我真的很努力做这个菜单……
which is also spelled wrong.
那个菜单也拼错了。
Give me back those 'manus'.
把那些‘菜单’还给我。
- You two kids sure know a lot about "Hungry Wars."
- 你们两个小孩对《饥饿战争》真了解。
- Yep, that's why we made a pact
- 是啊，所以我们立下誓言
to go see the new movie together.
一起去看看新电影。
We are "Hungry Wars" movie buddies.
我们是《饥饿战争》的电影伙伴。
- Secret Ganderk battle cry!
秘密的甘德克战斗口号！
both: Ganderk!
甘德克！
- Knock it off, you Gan-dorks.
别闹了，你们这些甘德克呆子。
Derek Moses just walked in.
德里克·摩西刚走进来。
- Look at him.
看他。
- He's so cool.
他真酷。
- Cooler than Monday night bingo.
比周一晚上的宾果游戏还酷。
- He might be the coolest kid in school, but I'm a close second.
他可能是学校里最酷的孩子，但我紧随其后。
Very close. Check this out.
非常接近。看看这个。
Moses, my man. Grab a seat.
摩西，我的兄弟。找个座位坐下。
- No, thanks. I prefer to stand.
不了，谢谢。我更喜欢站着。
It's one of my ten cool-mandments.
这是我十条酷规之一。
Always be slightly above the crowd.
永远要略高于人群。
- Let me try this.
让我试试这个。
[exhales sharply]
（深吸一口气）
Oh, he's good.
哦，他真厉害。
- So, what's the small talk du jour?
那么，今天的小话题是什么？
- Whoa, he speaks French.
哇，他会说法语。
- We're talking "Hungry Wars."
我们在聊《饥饿战争》。
- Yeah, we're seeing it tonight.
是的，我们今晚要看。
- Ooh, Dawn and Mack. This sounds serious.
哦，Dawn和Mack。听起来很严肃。
- No, it's nothing like that.
不，不是那样的。
- And what's it like?
那是什么样的？
I'm getting a small whiff of something uncool here.
我感觉到一点不太对劲的气息。
Wait. [sniffs]
等等。[嗅]
You're not going with your parents, are you?
你不是和你的父母一起去，对吧？
- No, it is definitely not like that.
不，绝对不是那样的。
- Good, 'cause that would be breaking
那就好，因为那会违反Moses的第一条酷规：永远不要和父母一起看电影。
Moses's cool-mandment number one:
摩西的酷诫第一条：
never see a movie with your parents.
绝不要和父母一起看电影。
- Please, we are way past that.
拜托，我们早就过了那个阶段。
We go to the mall without our parents, we stay home alone.
我们自己去商场，独自在家。
- We're very evolved.
我们进化得很好。
- We're hardly ever around our parents.
我们几乎不和父母在一起。
- Don't your parents own this place?
难道这个地方不是你父母开的吗？
- Ah, we just hang out here for free smoothies.
啊，我们只是来这里免费喝smoothie的。
- You're lying.
你在撒谎。
But in a cool way.
但撒得很酷。
Speaking of cool,
说到酷，
I'm going to leave you guys with cool-mandment number six:
我要给你们留下酷诫第六条：
always use your name in your exit line.
永远在你的告别语中使用你的名字。
Moses has to goses.
摩西得走了。
[clicks tongue]
- He's as cool as a loafer in October.
他就像十月的懒汉一样酷。
- Two grape smoothies.
两杯葡萄冰沙。
- Oh, hey, Mom, don't forget.
哦，嘿，妈妈，别忘了。
Mack and I are going to see "Hungry Wars" tonight.
麦克和我今晚要去看《饥饿战争》。
- Yep, we can't wait.
是的，我们等不及了。
- For what? To drop me off?
- 为了什么？送我一程吗？
- No, to see "Hungry Wars" with you guys.
- 不，是和你们一起去看《饥饿战争》。
- With who guys? - You guys.
- 和谁一起？ - 你们。
- It sounds like you're saying, "You guys." - We are.
- 听起来你是在说，“你们”。 - 是的。
Look, you're not old enough to go to the movies with a boy by yourself, silly.
听着，你还不够大，不能自己和一个男孩去看电影，傻瓜。
- But it's not a boy-girl thing. It's a movie buddy thing, silly.
- 但不是男孩女孩的事。是电影伙伴的事，傻瓜。
- Now it's a movie buddy family thing.
- 现在变成电影伙伴家庭的事了。
- Yeah, we're going to take the boys and make a night of it. - Which boys? - You boys.
- 是的，我们要带上男孩们，一起过个晚上。 - 哪些男孩？ - 你们男孩。
- Who boys? - You boys.
- 谁男孩？ - 你们男孩。
all: Oh, boy.
大家: 哦，天哪。
[upbeat music]
- ♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
- ♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
- ♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
[whistling]
♪ ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
- ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na na na na na na ♪
- ♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
♪ Na na na na na na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na na na na na na ♪
- ♪ 一，二 ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- There is no way I'm going to the movies with Mack, Mom, and Dad.
- 我绝对不会和麦克、妈妈和爸爸去看电影的。
- Me, neither.
- 我也不会。
I mean, it'd be breaking Moses's cool-mandment.
- 我的意思是，这会违反摩西的酷诫。
- If anyone sees me, then I won't be
- 如果有人看到我，那我就不会再是
the second-coolest kid in school anymore.
学校里第二酷的孩子了。
- And I won't be the 47th. We'll be laughing stocks.
- 而我也不会是第47酷的了。我们会成为笑柄。
- Okay, let's all stop pacing.
- 好了，我们都别走来走去了。
That's it, I have to text him and cancel.
就这样，我得给他发短信取消。
"Mack, I'm sorry, but I'm sick and I can't go tonight.
Mack，对不起，我生病了，今晚不能去。
[coughs]
（咳嗽声）
Let's see 'Hungry Wars' again soon, movie buddy."
我们改天再一起看《饥饿战争》，电影伙伴。
[coughs]
（咳嗽声）
And send.
发送。
There, crisis averted.
好了，危机解除了。
- Did you type your coughs?
你把咳嗽声也打上去了？
- Of course, it makes it more believable.
当然，这样更可信。
- Who's ready to get hungry?
谁准备好饿肚子了？
- Harper family movie night.
Harper家的电影之夜。
[blows horn]
[吹响号角]
- Uh, guys?
呃，伙计们？
Sorry to ruin whatever that is,
抱歉打断你们正在做的事情，
but Mack had to cancel,
但Mack不得不取消，
so guess we'll just have to stay home.
所以看来我们只能呆在家里了。
Not see him or any of our other friends.
既见不到他，也见不到我们的其他朋友。
- Aw, man.
哎，真糟糕。
- What a bummer.
真扫兴。
- Disappointment.
失望。
- Don't be disappointed. We'll just go without Mack. - Yeah.
别失望。我们没有Mack也可以去。 - 是的。
Harper family movie night.
哈珀家庭电影之夜。
[blows horn]
[吹喇叭声]
- But I promised Mack I wouldn't see "Hungry Wars" without him,
但我向麦克试过绝不会不带他去看《饥饿战争》,
and I can't break my movie buddy pact, so...
而且我不能违背我的电影伙伴誓言，所以...
- Oh, oh, totally get it.
哦，哦，完全理解。
Oh, don't worry, kids.
哦，孩子们别担心。
all: Aah.
啊！
- We'll just see something else. - Yeah. - [all gasping]
我们就看别的吧。
- We got to do something.
是啊。
- Uh, you know what's better than seeing something else?
我们得做点什么。
Seeing something else somewhere else.
换个地方看别的东西。
Like a different movie theater.
比如去不同的电影院。
- That's a great idea.
那是个好主意。
- So instead of going to our usual theater,
所以，我们不去我们常去的电影院，
why don't we go check out that new movie theater
我们为什么不去看看那个新开的电影院呢，
all the way over in Fort Collins...
就在科林斯堡那边...
[whispers] where no one we know will see us.
（低语）那里没有我们认识的人会看到我们。
- That is a great idea.
那真是个好主意。
- Harper family movie night and road trip.
哈珀家庭电影之夜和公路旅行。
[sputters]
（呛到）
- I don't know. Fort Collins is pretty far.
我不知道。Fort Collins 相当远。
- I heard they have a popcorn booth you stand in.
我听说他们有一个爆米花亭，你站在里面。
It blows popcorn all around you.
它会在你周围喷出爆米花。
Anything you catch, you eat.
你抓到的任何爆米花，你都可以吃。
- Anne, get the keys.
Anne，拿钥匙。
- No, but Tom-- - Anne, keys, now.
不，但是 Tom—— Anne，钥匙，现在。
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Man, this place was far.
天啊，这个地方真远。
- And totally worth it.
但绝对值得。
Behold,
看，
the Popcornado.
爆米花龙卷风。
- Ricky, I got to admit,
- 瑞奇，我得承认，
movie theater road trip was an impressive idea.
电影院公路旅行是个了不起的主意。
- I do put the imp in impressive.
- 我的确让了不起变得更有趣。
- And the best part is,
- 而最棒的是，
Mom and Dad can embarrass us all they want,
爸妈可以尽情让我们难堪，
'cause we're in a place where no one knows us.
因为我们在一个没人认识我们的地方。
- Except Natlee.
- 除了娜特莉。
- And Dooley.
- 还有杜利。
- And Xander.
还有Xander。
And Callie and Tessa.
还有Callie和Tessa。
- Everyone knows us!
大家都认识我们！
- This was a terrible plan.
这个计划糟透了。
- All right, just calm down.
好吧，冷静点。
We don't want to draw attention to ourselves.
我们不想引起注意。
- Six tickets to "Triassic Jungle."
六张《三叠纪丛林》的票。
Can I get a Harper family movie night?
我能来个Harper家族电影之夜吗？
[blows horn]
（吹喇叭）
- She brought the horn.
她带了喇叭。
- We got to get them in the theater before she blows again.
我们必须在他们再次吹响号角之前让他们进入剧院。
- Oh.
哦。
Hey, Mom, the theater's filling up.
嘿，妈妈，剧院里人越来越多了。
We should probably get in there.
我们可能应该进去了。
- Come on, Dad.
快点，爸爸。
- But I'm in line for the Popcornado.
但我还在排队买爆米花龙卷风。
- If we don't hurry up, all the good seats will be gone.
如果我们不快点，好座位就都没了。
- And you know how you hate sitting in the back of the theater.
而且你知道你有多讨厌坐在剧院的后排。
- And then you get all whiney.
然后你就会开始抱怨。
- The kids are right, Tom.
孩子们说得对，汤姆。
You do get a little whiney when you don't get what you want.
你确实会在得不到想要的东西时变得有点抱怨。
- But we got a half hour till the movie starts.
但电影还有半小时才开始。
I want to go into the Popcornado now...
我现在就想去排队买Popcornado...
Oh, I see what you mean.
哦，我明白你的意思了。
- Tell you what, if you hurry and get us good seats,
这样吧，如果你快点帮我们找到好座位，
we'll save your spot in the Popcornado line.
我们就帮你保留在Popcornado队伍中的位置。
- Here, take our coats and save our seats.
来，拿着我们的外套占座。
- Oh. Oh. Okay.
哦，哦，好的。
- All right now, run along now,
好了，现在快跑，
last one to the theater's a rotten egg.
最后一个到剧院的是坏蛋。
- We're adults.
- 我们是成年人。
We don't care about being the rotten egg, right, Anne?
我们不在乎成为坏蛋，对吧，Anne？
I'm always the rotten egg.
我总是那个坏蛋。
- Okay, as long as they're in there and we're out here,
- 好吧，只要他们在里面而我们在外面，
we're good.
我们就没事。
- Not good. Mack is here.
- 不太好。Mack在这里。
- The whole school's here.
- 整个学校的人都在这里。
- Wait, is anybody else mad that none of these people called us?
- 等等，有没有人觉得这些人没给我们打电话很生气？
- I can't let Mack see me.
- 我不能让Mack看到我。
He'll know I lied.
他会知道我撒谎了。
Here, I'm going to go into our theater.
这里，我要去我们的剧院。
You guys keep an eye on him and text me if he's heading my way.
你们盯着他，如果他朝我这边来就给我发短信。
- Okay, quick quaddle.
好的，快点儿。
What's the best way to follow Mack without him seeing us?
跟踪Mack而不被他发现的最佳方法是什么？
- You guys having a secret conversation?
你们在秘密交谈吗？
- Uh, no.
呃，没有。
We're not having a secret conversation.
我们没有秘密交谈。
The more the merrier, buddy.
人越多越热闹，伙计。
- Well, you see, cool-mandment number three says
嗯，你看，酷规则第三条说
to always trust your gut, and right now,
要永远相信你的直觉，而现在，
my gut's telling me you guys are up to something uncool.
我的直觉告诉我，你们在搞什么不酷的事情。
- No, this is just how we talk.
不，我们就是这样说话的。
- Anyway, we have to get going.
反正，我们得走了。
- Why?
为什么？
You're not here with your parents, are you?
你不是和父母一起来的，对吧？
- What? - No way.
什么？——不可能。
- Parents are for kids.
父母是给小孩的。
We're just chilling in the lobby.
我们只是在休息室里放松。
- Trying to decide which video games to play
试图决定玩哪些电子游戏
to attract more sweet, parentless honeys.
来吸引更多甜美、无父母的蜜蜂。
- The answer's simple: whatever game Moses is playing.
答案很简单：摩西在玩什么游戏，我们就玩什么。
Let's go. [clicks tongue]
走吧。
- [sighs]
（叹气）
- Check it out, Anne. They have a lobby cam.
看，安妮。他们有个大堂摄像头。
Oh. Oh.
哦。哦。
Oh, this is--
哦，这是——
Look at this amateur in the Popcornado.
看看这个在Popcornado里的新手。
His technique is terrible.
他的技术太糟糕了。
He should be using his mouth, like this.
他应该用嘴，像这样。
You gotta...
你得……
- No, honey, don't. Please, honey.
不，亲爱的，别这样。请，亲爱的。
Oh, excuse me. I'm sorry.
哦，对不起，打扰一下。
Those seats are taken. Yeah.
那些座位已经有人了。是的。
- You're supposed to be saving my spot in the Popcornado line.
你应该是在帮我占爆米花风暴的队。
- Oh, don't worry. The boys are saving it.
哦，别担心。孩子们在占着。
- Really?
真的吗？
Because it looks like they're playing video games.
因为看起来他们正在玩游戏。
- Which we both know
我们都知道
is not what they're supposed to be doing.
这不是他们应该做的事。
Let me go take care of this. - Mm.
让我去处理一下。
- I give you guys one job.
我只给你们一个任务。
And by the way, Mom and Dad can totally
顺便说一句，爸爸妈妈完全可以看到你们...
see you...
稍后。
later.
因为他们现在肯定不在这里和我们在一起。
'Cause they're certainly not here with us now.
怎么回事？你们都表现得怪怪的。
- What's going on? You guys are all acting weird.
而且摩西对这种事情很敏感。
And Moses got a noses for that kind of thing.
我们一直都是这样。
- This is how we always act.
你得记住，我们远没有你那么酷。
You got to remember, we're not nearly as cool as you.
说到不酷的事情，
- Speaking of things that are not cool,
我刚看到玛雅和杰拉尔德·丁克勒拿着胡萝卜条。
I just saw Mya and Gerald Dinkler with carrot sticks.
我刚看到迈亚和杰拉尔德·丁克勒拿着胡萝卜条。
- [gasps] - Healthy snacks at the movies?
- [倒抽气] - 在电影院吃健康零食？
Moses opposes.
摩西反对。
- Where's Mack?
- 麦克的去向？
You guys were supposed to be keeping an eye on him.
你们应该看着他的。
- He's right there.
- 他就在那儿。
You're welcome.
不用谢。
- Wait, he's seeing "Hungry Wars" without me?
- 等等，他看《饥饿战争》没带我？
- Well, if it makes you feel any better,
- 好吧，如果这能让你感觉好点，
I don't think he saw you.
我觉得他没看到你。
- It doesn't make me feel any better.
- 这并没有让我感觉好一点。
He broke our movie buddy pact.
他打破了我们的电影伙伴协议。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- Mack and I had a movie pact.
- 我和Mack有过电影协议。
- Here we go with the pacing again.
- 我们又开始急匆匆了。
- We were supposed to be movie buddies.
- 我们本应该是电影伙伴。
- In his defense, you do have a terrible text-cough.
- 在他辩护一下，你的短信咳嗽确实很糟糕。
- And he's not seeing it at your usual theater
- 而且他不是在你常去的影院看的
where you might have found out and gotten upset.
那里你可能早就发现了然后生气了。
That's pretty considerate.
那真是挺体贴的。
- And you did lie to him first.
而且你先对他撒了谎。
So I'm kind of Team Mack here.
所以我有点站在Mack这边。
- I lied to protect our movie pact.
我撒谎是为了保护我们的电影约定。
He broke it.
他破坏了它。
You know what? I'm going in.
你知道吗？我要进去了。
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
哇，哇，哇。
You don't want to face him when you're this mad.
你不想在这么生气的时候面对他。
- Yeah. Pace it off, mama.
是啊。冷静一下，妈妈。
- No. I'm going to call him.
不。我要给他打电话。
- That's a worse idea.
那是个更糟糕的主意。
You know things don't go well when you call angry.
你知道当你生气时打电话不会有好结果。
- I believe the term is Dawn-dialing.
我相信那个术语叫‘愤怒拨号’。
- Yeah, remember last Christmas when Aunt Gilda gave you that juggling lesson as a gift?
记得去年圣诞节，吉尔达阿姨送你杂耍课作为礼物吗？
And you thanked her with a big, fat Dawn-dial.
你用一次愤怒的电话感谢了她。
- She still won't take any of our calls.
她到现在还不接我们的电话。
- Who gives somebody one lesson?
谁会给别人上一节课作为礼物？
You can't learn to juggle in 45 minutes.
你不可能在45分钟内学会杂耍。
It can't be done.
这是不可能的。
- Just give me the phone, Dawn.
把电话给我，Dawn。
- Guys, don't worry.
伙计们，别担心。
This is not an Aunt Gilda situation.
这不是吉尔达阿姨那种情况。
Voicemail.
语音信箱。
I'm just going to express my disappointment
我只是想表达我的失望
and ask him to call me later to discuss it.
并请他稍后给我回电话讨论这件事。
Hey, Mack. It's Dawn.
嘿，麦克。我是道恩。
How's it going...
最近怎么样...
is what I would have said if I wasn't so mad.
如果我不这么生气，我就会这么说。
I can't believe you went to "Hungry Wars" without me.
真不敢相信你没带我去‘饥饿战争’。
- Should have taken the phone.
本该拿走电话的。
- That's right, Mr. I'm-gonna-go-to-Fort-Collins-
就是啊，福尔柯林斯先生，以为没人会看见你
so-nobody-will-see-me.
我在布里斯特六影院，跟我爸妈一起
I'm at the Brister Six with my parents.
至少她没说跟我们一起
- At least she didn't say us. - And my brothers.
还有我兄弟们
- Hey, we made the message.
嘿，是我们一起留的信息呢
- And I just saw you go into the movie
我刚看到你进了电影院
you and I made a pact to see together.
就是我们约好要一起看的那部电影
But I guess our friendship doesn't mean anything to you,
但我想咱俩的友谊对你来说啥也不是
so guess what, mister?
所以你知道吗，先生？
You're no longer my movie buddy.
你不再是我的电影伙伴了
You are my movie...
enemy.
Dawn out.
What have I done?
- Classic Dawn-dial.
- That she dragged us into.
- Yeah, now everyone's going to know we're here
with our parents, too.
We're doomed. Thanks a lot, Dawn.
- Don't blame me.
You guys should have never let me Dawn-dial.
你们当初就不该让我用Dawn的方式拨号。
You know what?
你们知道吗？
I'm going to call all three of you right now
我现在就要给你们三个打电话
and tell you how angry I am.
告诉你们我有多生气。
- Dawn, stop.
- Dawn，住手。
- Oh, Mack's coming back out.
- 哦，Mack又出来了。
- Hey, I went into the wrong theater.
- 嘿，我进错电影院了。
Um, I'm not seeing "Hungry Wars."
呃，我看的不是《饥饿战争》。
I mean, I want to, but I'd never see it without my movie buddy.
我是说，我想看，但我绝不会在没有我的电影伙伴的情况下看。
Uh, where's "Triassic Jungle"?
呃，《三叠纪丛林》在哪里？
Over there? Thanks.
在那边吗？谢谢。
- Oh, no. Mack's heading in our theater.
哦，不。Mack正朝我们的剧院走来。
- Oh, this is bad.
哦，这可不妙。
- I have to delete that message before he hears it.
我得在他听到之前删除那条消息。
You guys have to help me.
你们得帮我。
- This is not our problem.
这不是我们的问题。
You dialed your bed, now you have to...
你拨通了你的床，现在你得……
lie on your phone...
躺在你的手机上……
bed.
床上。
- That doesn't make any sense.
这说不通。
- I would have thought of something that made more sense but Aunt Gilda only gave me that one improv lesson.
- 我本可以想出一个更有意义的方法，但吉尔达阿姨只给了我那一节即兴课。
[exhales]
[叹气]
The point is, you have to get Mack's phone yourself.
关键是，你得自己去拿麦克的电话。
- Why do you need Mack's phone?
- 你为什么需要麦克的电话？
all: Aah!
所有人: 啊！
- I didn't say Mack's phone.
- 我没说麦克的电话。
I said Zach's cone.
我说的是扎克的锥。
- Yeah, our friend Zach lost his cone
- 是的，我们的朋友扎克丢了他的锥
and we were helping him find it.
我们正在帮他找。
- What kind of cone?
- 什么样的锥？
- Ice cream. - Dog.
- 冰淇淋。 - 狗。
- Snow. - He's a cone guy.
- 雪。 - 他是个锥形物体爱好者。
- You know, my gut tells me you guys are up to something,
- 你知道，我的直觉告诉我你们在搞什么鬼，
and I'm going to find out what's going on.
- 我一定要弄清楚是怎么回事。
Moses is going to go find Mack's phoneses.
- 摩西要去找到麦克的电话。
- He doesn't knowses where Mack goeses.
- 他不知道麦克去哪儿了。
- Can we please stop rhyming?
- 我们能不能别押韵了？
- I supposes.
- 我想可以。
All right, just follow my lead.
- 好吧，跟着我走。
Hurry, Mack went this way!
- 快点，麦克往这边走了！
- Nice try, Harpers, but Moses ain't slowses.
- 试得不错，哈珀家的小子们，但摩西可不慢。
- He fell for it.
- 他上当了。
Okay, now stay closes--sorry.
好吧，现在保持靠近——抱歉。
Okay, there's Mack.
好了，那是麦克的。
- Yeah.
- 是的。
- Right by Mom and Dad.
- 就在爸爸妈妈旁边。
- How are we going to get his phone without them seeing us?
- 我们怎么才能在他父母没发现的情况下拿到他的手机呢？
- Lobby cam.
- 大厅的摄像头。
I got an idea. Follow me.
我有个主意。跟我来。
- Should do it.
- 应该能行。
- Don't you think you should just sit down at the end?
你不觉得你应该直接坐在最后吗？
- [chuckles]
（轻笑）
No need, Anne.
不需要，Anne。
It's common theater etiquette
这是剧院常见的礼仪
that an article of clothing indicates a saved seat.
用一件衣物表示保留座位。
- Hmm, well, you might want to tell that guy.
嗯，那你可能需要告诉那个人。
- The what--how--what--no, no.
什么——怎么——什么——不，不。
I don't know what kind of theater etiquette you're used to, but in my America,
我不知道你习惯什么样的剧院礼仪，但在我的美国，
a sweater on a seat means, "Get lost, hippie."
座位上的毛衣意味着，“走开，嬉皮士。”
Let's move. Come on.
我们走吧。快点。
What's going on?
怎么了？
Oh.
哦。
Dang it.
该死。
I'm C6.
我是C6。
- Yes!
是的！
- Aah.
啊。
Lucky Fort Collins kid.
幸运的Fort Collins孩子。
Popcornado, full head of hair.
爆米花风暴，满头秀发。
Neither one's going to last forever!
这两样都不会永远持续的！
- Dicky, you're supposed to dump the popcorn out.
Dicky，你应该把爆米花倒出来。
- Why would I waste popcorn?
- 我为什么要浪费爆米花？
- Because now you can't see anything.
- 因为现在你什么都看不见了。
- I can see clouds. - That's popcorn.
- 我能看见云。 - 那是爆米花。
- Sweet!
- 太棒了！
- Oh, here he comes.
- 哦，他来了。
- Hey, uh, I was called up here.
- 嘿，呃，我被叫到这里来的。
Seat A6.
座位A6。
- Yes. You're the big winner.
- 是的。你是大奖得主。
- Who are you guys?
- 你们是谁？
- Uh, Butterpop. - Popcorn Peeps.
- 呃，黄油爆。 - 爆米花小队。
- Tub Buddies.
- 浴缸伙伴。
- This isn't about us. This is about you.
- 这不是关于我们的，这是关于你的。
It's prize time, so let's get popping.
现在是颁奖时间，让我们开始吧。
- Wait, why does that sign say "back in ten"?
- 等等，为什么那个牌子写着“十分钟后回来”？
- Those are just instructions.
- 那些只是指示。
Back in and count to ten.
回来并数到十。
- Oh, and uh, give us your phone so, you know,
- 哦，还有，呃，把你的手机给我们，你知道的，
we can take your picture.
我们可以给你拍照。
- Oh, man, I wish my movie buddy were here to see this.
- 哦，伙计，我希望我的电影伙伴能在这里看到这一幕。
- How's the plan going?
- 计划进行得怎么样？
- Okay, in you go. - Huh?
- 好了，进去吧。 - 嗯？
- Come on, delete.
- 快点，删除。
- What's taking so long?
- 怎么这么慢？
- My fingers are all buttery.
- 我的手指都是黄油。
- My face is all buttery.
- 我的脸都是黄油。
[Popcornado runs]
[爆米花龙卷风跑动]
- Give it to me. - No, give it to me.
- 给我。 - 不，给我。
I know it's you, Harpers.
我知道是你，哈珀斯。
- It is not us. We are popcorn robots.
- 不是我们。我们是爆米花机器人。
- Beep bop beep bop beep beep.
- 哔啵哔啵哔啵哔。
- Moses, what are you doing with my phone?
- 摩西，你拿我手机干嘛？
- He doesn't have your phone.
- 他没有拿你手机。
We do! Huddle!
是我们拿的！快聚在一起！
- I know one of you has it.
- 我知道你们中有人拿了。
- Yes, but which one?
- 是的，但到底是哪一个？
Scatter!
散开！
- Hey. - Not cool.
- 嘿。 - 不酷。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
♪ ♪
♪
- Since no one here respects
- 既然这里没人尊重
loosely-draped articles of clothing,
松散披挂的衣物，
looks like I'm going to have to lock it down
看来我得用一件结实的毛衣-夹克-围巾屏障来固定它。
with a secure sweater-jacket-scarf barrier.
是的。
Yeah.
没有什么能穿过那个宝贝。
Nothing's getting through that baby.
- 哦，除了那个人。
- Oh, except that guy.
对不起，打扰一下。
Excuse me, I'm sorry.
我们为我们的孩子保留这些。
We're saving those for our children.
我们的孩子在哪儿？
Where are our children?
- 这四个座位从我进来就一直空着。
- These four seats have been empty since I came in.
我觉得你占着它们。
I think you're hogging them.
我觉得你占着它们了。
So, until your "children" come back...
所以，直到你的“孩子们”回来...
- [gasps] - I'm going to sit here.
我打算坐在这里。
- No, no, no, no. Do not air quote our children.
不，不，不，不。不要用引号说我们的孩子。
- Our children are totally "real."
我们的孩子绝对是“真实的”。
- Okay, honey, if you air-quote "real"
好吧，亲爱的，如果你用引号说“真实的”
it means they're not real.
那就意味着他们不是真实的。
- [huffs]
哼！
"Does it?"
“是吗？”
- Yes, come on.
是的，快点。
- Where am I going? Where am I going?
我要去哪里？我要去哪里？
What's happening?
发生了什么？
- Oh! Oh! Ah. Oh.
哦！哦！啊。哦。
My head!
我的头！
Oh, ah.
哦，啊。
- See? Those are our kids "right there."
看？那些就是我们的孩子‘就在那里’。
- Still wrong.
还是不对。
- See, everyone?
看，大家？
Told you we came here to the movies with our kids.
告诉过你们我们是带着孩子来看电影的。
Ha ha!
哈哈！
- Yep, now everybody knows.
是的，现在大家都知道了。
- I knew it.
我就知道。
You Harpers broke cool-mandment number one.
你们哈珀家打破了酷规第一条。
- Dawn, I thought you were sick.
Dawn，我以为你生病了。
You typed "cough" and everything.
你还打了“咳嗽”什么的。
What's going on?
怎么回事？
- When I asked my parents if I could see "Hungry Wars" with you they said only if they chaperoned,
当我问我父母是否可以和你一起看《饥饿战争》时，他们说只有在他们陪同的情况下才可以，
and I was too embarrassed to break cool-mandment number one.
而我太尴尬了，不敢打破酷规第一条。
- So you put on a popcorn bucket head and stole my phone?
所以你戴上爆米花桶头，偷了我的手机？
- Only because when I saw you go into "Hungry Wars"
只是因为当我看到你进入《饥饿战争》时，
I thought you were seeing it without me,
我以为你要自己去看，
and then I got kind of mad and Dawn-dialed you.
然后我就有点生气，用Dawn模式给你打了电话。
- Like Aunt Gilda?
- 像Gilda阿姨那样？
- Worse.
- 更糟。
- I'm sorry, Mack.
- 对不起，Mack。
I should have just told you the truth.
我应该直接告诉你真相的。
- Thanks.
- 谢谢。
- For the record, I was Team Mack all the way.
- 顺便说一句，我一直都是支持Mack的。
- None of this would have happened if we hadn't been so worried
- 如果不是我们那么担心
about being seen at the movies with our parents.
和父母一起看电影会被看到，这一切都不会发生。
- Let's go.
走吧。
Why don't you go sit with your "friends?"
你为什么不跟你那些“朋友”坐一起？
Hey, kids. - Hi.
嘿，孩子们。- 嗨。
- I get it.
- 我明白了。
I only went into "Hungry Wars" because I saw Moses,
我之所以会进《饥饿战争》，是因为我看见了摩西,
and I didn't want him to see me with...
我不想让他看到我和…
my Mom.
我妈妈在一起。
Sorry, Mom.
对不起，妈妈。
- You know, I thought you guys were cool,
- 你们知道吗，我原以为你们很酷，
but you've given me no choice
但你们没给我别的选择
but to let everyone know just how uncool you are.
但我要让大家知道你们有多么不酷。
- Then you'll have to let everyone know how uncool I am, too.
那你就得让大家知道我有多不酷。
I'm with my parents.
我和我的父母在一起。
- Natalie?
娜塔莉？
- It's Natlee.
是娜特莉。
- Ugh.
呃。
You guys aren't the only ones.
你们不是唯一这样做的。
- Oscar?
奥斯卡？
- Wow, we all came this far
哇，我们都走这么远了
just to avoid being seen with our parents?
只是为了避免被看到和父母在一起？
- Am I the only kid cool enough to be here without my parents?
- 我是唯一一个没有父母陪伴还能这么酷的孩子吗？
- Derek Norman Moses,
- 德里克·诺曼·摩西，
stop pretending you're unsupervised.
别装作没人管你的样子。
You know the only reason you get to roam around here by yourself
你知道你之所以能一个人在这里晃荡，
is because I work here.
唯一的原因是因为我在这里工作。
Now get back to that break room
现在回到休息室去，
and do your homework.
做你的作业。
- Come on, Mom.
- 拜托，妈妈。
You're making me look so uncool.
你让我看起来很没面子。
[sighs]
[叹气]
- Stop that. - Ugh.
- 别那样。 - 呃。
- Norman.
- 诺曼。
- Okay, well, now that that's settled,
- 好了，既然事情解决了，
why don't we grab our seats?
我们为什么不找个座位坐下呢？
The movie's about to start.
电影就要开始了。
- Animals.
- 动物。
- Oh, then why don't we all see if we can get into "Hungry Wars"?
- 哦，那我们为什么不试试看能不能进《饥饿战争》呢？
- Sounds good, movie buddy.
- 听起来不错，电影伙伴。
- There's just one thing we need to do first.
- 不过我们得先做一件事。
- Yeah.
- 是的。
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
- That's our Dad.
- 那是我们的爸爸。
- [blows horn]
- [吹喇叭]
- Her, we do not know.
- 她，我们不认识。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪